exoticjourney.com 2014-02-09

# ExoticJourney.com | Privacy Policy

Exotic Journey created the policies on our site, so that our users can easily find and comprehend our privacy and terms of use policy. We believe we have a responsibility to our users to present the kinds of information we collect when you visit Exotic Journey. That way there are no surprises. By using Exotic Journey, you agree to adhere to the policies listed below.

#### Information We Collect

Exotic Journey collects two types of information: personal information that you voluntarily provide us and information that is automatically collected, but is not personally identifiable. We log the information you submit to us through users submissions and the non-identifiable statistical information we gather when you visit Exotic Journey.

Users submissions are anything a user voluntarily posts to Exotic Journey. This includes: tips, comments and feedback left to Exotic Journey. Users submissions may be public information the site and logged for our records. However, this information will never include personal information unless you willingly provide it with your submission. Do not include information you wish to keep private in your submissions.

We’ve created a login, so that our users can get the information that is most relevant to their interested. When a user logs in Exotic Journey, they will need to register their name and email. Login systems give us the opportunity to better provide content and customer service for our users.

Some information is automatically collected when you visit Exotic Journey. This information includes your: IP address, browser type, pages viewed, searches made and timestamp information regarding your visit. This information will never include your personal information.

Most websites require the use of Cookies. Exotic Journey is no different. Cookies are used to improve the user experience by storing site preferences, login information and other statistical information. Cookies are small pieces of alphanumeric data that is sent from your browser to your hard drive. When you enable the use of Cookies, you will see all of what Exotic Journey has to offer. You may decide to disable your Cookies, but that will limit your use of Exotic Journey.

#### Third Parties

Users put a certain amount of trust into a website to protect their information. Because of this, Exotic Journey will never lease, rent, sell or trade your information. We do everything in our power to protect your information

We may display advertisements from third parties on our site. We are not affiliated with these sites and are not responsible for the protection of your privacy when you visit these sites. When visiting other websites, please exercise caution.

Exotic Journey may transfer non-personally identifiable, statistical information to our current or future affiliates. These affiliates may be our parent company, joint ventures, subsidiaries, or companies under common or future common control. These companies are expected to abide by our privacy policy. You will be protected just the same.

We will only share your personal information if we are required to do by means of the law. This includes: court orders, subpoenas, warrants and to protect the public and our users.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act

While we cannot guarantee the protection of your privacy, we have done everything in our power to protect it. We comply with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. Your information will never be shared with outside parties without your consent.

#### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act

We believe the safety of children should be a priority. That being said, we comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. Our site is not marketed to children under the age of 13 and will not collect information from people under the age of 13. It is our duty to protect children.

#### Unsubscribe and Updates

Exotic Journey is not the same without you. However, you may unsubscribe at any point by visiting the Unsubscribe page. This will remove you from future notifications and communication from Exotic Journey.

If there are ever updates to this policy, they will be posted on this page. If you have any questions, please visit our Contact Us page.
